Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers 1931-2016 MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Novels
    - Ragtime (original draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime (original draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime (notes), undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime (revised draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime (revised draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections), undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime (incomplete draft with corrections), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Ragtime (incomplete copy of draft with corrections), undated (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime (xerox copy of pages 84-119), undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited draft, 3/4/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited draft, 3/4/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime (galleys, 3/6/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Ragtime (galleys, 3/6/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited galleys, 4/9/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited galleys, 4/9/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (original draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (original draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (draft by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (second draft, first revision by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections by Michael Weller and E.L.Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (copy), undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime-musical script (first draft), undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime-musical script (early draft with correspondence, 4/11/1994) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime-musical script (marked "GHD Ragtime notes" 2/10/1995) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 8/26/1995) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 2/16/1996) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 5/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 7/26/1996) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/17/1996) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/18/1996) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 3/30/1997) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 12/4/1997) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, not dated), undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Loon Lake (early drafts and notes), undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Loon Lake (partial second draft), undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Loon Lake (partial second draft), undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Loon Lake (partial second draft), undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Loon Lake (third draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Loon Lake (third draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Loon Lake (third draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Loon Lake (third draft)-Part 4, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Loon Lake (third draft)-Part 5, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Loon Lake (fragment with corrections), undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 4, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 5, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 6, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 7, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified drafts with corrections)-Part 8, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Loon Lake (incomplete fragments with corrections), undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Loon Lake (fragment with corrections), undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified xerox copy draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Loon Lake (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Loon Lake (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Loon Lake (first pass galley masters), undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Loon Lake (second pass galley masters)-Part 3, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified galleys)-Part 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified galleys)-Part 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified galleys)-Part 3, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified galleys), undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Loon Lake (unidentified galleys), undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Loon Lake (repros), undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Loon Lake (blues), undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Loon Lake (Polish translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Loon Lake (Polish translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Loon Lake-screenplay (hand-written draft with corrections), undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Loon Lake-screenplay (draft fragments with corrections), undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Loon Lake-screenplay (xerox copy draft), undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Three Screenplays by E.L. Doctorow-Daniel, Ragtime, Loon Lake (annotated Paul Levine interview), undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - World's Fair (original draft), undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - World's Fair (notes), undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - World's Fair (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - World's Fair (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - World's Fair (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - World's Fair (second draft with notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - World's Fair (second draft with notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - World's Fair (second draft with notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - World's Fair (second draft xerox copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - World's Fair (second draft xerox copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - World's Fair (marked "final draft [3rd?]")-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - World's Fair (marked "final draft [3rd?]")-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - World's Fair (marked "final draft [3rd?]")-Part 3, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - World's Fair (typescript with corrections) [1 of 5], 1985 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - World's Fair (typescript with corrections) [2 of 5], 1985 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - World's Fair (typescript with corrections) [3 of 5], 1985 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - World's Fair (typescript with corrections) [4 of 5], 1985 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - World's Fair (typescript with corrections) [5 of 5], 1985 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - World's Fair (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - World's Fair (unidentified drafts), undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - World's Fair (partial unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - World's Fair (first pass galley masters fragment), undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - World's Fair (introduction for Franklin Mint first edition of World's Fair), undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - World's Fair (French translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - World's Fair (French translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - World's Fair (Italian translation), undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - World's Fair (unidentified translation), undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Billy Bathgate (notebook and notes), undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified drafts with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified drafts with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified drafts with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified drafts with corrections and notes)-Part 4, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections) [1 of 3], undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections) [2 of 3], undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified draft with corrections) [3 of 3], undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Billy Bathgate (incomplete draft with corrections), undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Billy Bathgate (incomplete annotated draft) [1 of 2], undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Billy Bathgate (incomplete annotated draft) [2 of 2], undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Billy Bathgate (late draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Billy Bathgate (late draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Billy Bathgate (second-to-last draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Billy Bathgate (second-to-last draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Billy Bathgate (introduction), undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Billy Bathgate (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Billy Bathgate (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Billy Bathgate (setting copy)-Part 3, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Billy Bathgate (uncorrected galleys)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Billy Bathgate (uncorrected galleys)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Billy Bathgate (uncorrected galleys)-Part 3, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Billy Bathgate (galleys with corrections), undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Billy Bathgate (Random House galleys)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Billy Bathgate (Random House galleys)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Billy Bathgate (first pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Billy Bathgate (first pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Billy Bathgate (first pass galley masters)-Part 3, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Billy Bathgate (second pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Billy Bathgate (second pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Billy Bathgate (Italian translation), undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Billy Bathgate (Polish translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Billy Bathgate (Polish translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Billy Bathgate (Romanian translation), undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Billy Bathgate (Russian translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Billy Bathgate (Russian translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Billy Bathgate (Spanish translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Billy Bathgate (Spanish translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Billy Bathgate (Spanish translation)-Part 3, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Billy Bathgate (unidentified translation), undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (first draft, 11/1989) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (revised first draft, 3/1990) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (second draft, 5/1990) (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (revised second draft, 5/25/1990) (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (third draft, 6/15/1990) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (third draft, 6/15/1990) (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (fourth draft, 9/14/1990) (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (revised fourth draft with shot schedule)—Part 1, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (revised fourth draft with shot schedule)—Part 2, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (incomplete revised fourth draft with shot schedule), undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (Doctorow's comments and revisions), undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (fragment with corrections), undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (unidentified draft with the Notice of Tentative Writing Credits, 2/20/1991) (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Billy Bathgate-screenplay by Tom Stoppard (five pages of script), undated (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Billy Bathgate (treatment by Jim Kouf, 3/29/1989) (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Billy Bathgate screenplay Dustin Hoffman memo [1 of 3], 1991 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Billy Bathgate screenplay Dustin Hoffman memo [2 of 3], 1991 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Billy Bathgate screenplay Dustin Hoffman memo [3 of 3], 1991 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Three Complete Novels: Billy Bathgate, World's Fair, Loon Lake (publication galleys, 12/1993) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - The Waterworks (marked "1st printed draft pgs.1-49"), undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - The Waterworks (early draft title The Soul)-Part 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - The Waterworks (early draft title The Soul)-Part 2, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 4, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 5, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - The Waterworks (draft titled The Soul with corrections)-Part 6, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - The Waterworks (second draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - The Waterworks (second draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - The Waterworks (second draft with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - The Waterworks (various fragments and printouts with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - The Waterworks (various fragments and printouts with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - The Waterworks (various fragments with corrections), undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - The Waterworks (drafts with corrections and notes), undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - The Waterworks (drafts with corrections and notes), undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - The Waterworks (drafts with corrections and notes), undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - The Waterworks (Chapters 1, 6, 7, 13, 16, 18, 20 with corrections), undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Waterworks (notebook, notes, and manuscript pages, mostly from The Waterworks)—Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - The Waterworks (notebook, notes, and manuscript pages, mostly from The Waterworks)—Part 2, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 4, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 5, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified drafts, some with corrections)-Part 6, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - The Waterworks (miscellaneous manuscript pages), undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - The Waterworks (manuscript fragment), undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - The Waterworks (incomplete draft with corrections), undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft fragment) [1 of 2] (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - The Waterworks (unidentified draft fragment) [2 of 2] (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - The Waterworks (copy-edited draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - The Waterworks (copy-edited draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - The Waterworks (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - The Waterworks (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Waterworks (first pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - The Waterworks (second pass galley masters)-Part 1, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - The Waterworks (second pass galley masters)-Part 2, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - The Waterworks (third pass galley masters fragment), undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - The Waterworks (unbound third addition), undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - The Waterworks (Audio Book script), undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - The Waterworks (Danish translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - The Waterworks (Danish translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - The Waterworks (Finnish translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - The Waterworks (Finnish translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - The Waterworks (French translation), undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - The Waterworks (Portuguese translation)-Part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - The Waterworks (Portuguese translation)-Part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - The Waterworks (Russian translation), undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - The Waterworks (translation titled Spökbussen), undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - The Waterworks (translation titled Vodárna)-Part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - The Waterworks (translation titled Vodárna)-Part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - City of God (notes), undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - City of God (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - City of God (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - City of God (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - City of God (unidentified uncorrected draft), undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - City of God (annotated typescript draft) [1 of 2], undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - City of God (annotated typescript draft) [2 of 2], undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - City of God (incomplete draft, typescript, notes), undated (Box 73, Folder 14)